Spear Cutie
I look up to the stars
and reach for the sky.
I believe in tomorrow if we try!
Come on, let's go, everybody!
Oh, we share the music!
We share the music!
Come on, let's go, baby, baby!
Oh, we share the one dream!
Come on, let's go, everybody!
Oh, we share the good times!
We share the good times.
Come on, let's go, baby, baby!
Oh, we share the one world.
It's hard to see for you and me.
Through the darkness
that is in this world.
So hard to see or to believe.
In where we need to go.
Yes, you and me, it's true that we.
Feel the rush brought up by this world.
Through head to feet, I feel the beat.
Getting me to walk on, oh yeah.
Share the music, no matter what.
Share the one dream, believe in yourself.
Share the good times, take my hand now.
Share the one world now.
I look up to the stars
and reach for the sky.
No matter what, I'll
try no matter how high.
So let us go beyond, far and wide.
I believe in tomorrow if we try.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Come on, let's go, everybody!
Oh, we share the music.
We share the music.
Come on, let's go, baby, baby.
Oh, we share the one world. No!
Oh, as we chase, we're being chased.
From the top we go on straight and wild.
We're on our way, I've got to say.
Hey, I want to share your style.
Now here it starts, so don't lose heart.
They're bound to lose to this flavor.
From boot to hood, I feel so good.
I will be free to be, oh yeah.
Share the music, even if I.
Share the one dream, I know where you are.
Share the good times,
share the one world now.
I look up to the stars.
And reach for the sky.
No matter what.
I'll try no matter how high.
So let us go.
Beyond far and wide.
I believe in tomorrow.
If we try.
I know that you are there.
Just on the other side.
Wait there for me.
Soon it will be you and I.
Then let us go.
Beyond far and wide.
I believe in the one world.
If we try.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Come on, let's go, everybody.
Oh, we share the music.
Come on, let's go, baby, baby.
Oh, we share the one world?
So good!
Yep, Hodgkin's octopus fritters
are the best in the world!
I can't stop eating and you can't make me?
This stuff is amazing!
You're great. What?
That flavor.
That's a brilliant idea, turning
your super-tool food stall.
This is the first time I've had the
pleasure of eating octopus fish.
They really are delectable.
My stomach is about to burst.
Or get quiet if I had one
of the bird buddies. You!
You can eat as much as you want.
It's on the house.
It's the very least we can do to show
a little gratitude for saving us.
These have rice cakes in them, and
these are made with soup stock.
Be careful now, they're really hot.
So, Nami, what do you think?
Are they good?
Um, is it...
does it taste okay?
Listen, don't think I'm going to forgive
you because of something silly like this.
No, no, of course not.
That's not what I meant.
I just wanted to know if you
think it tastes good, honestly.
That's all I swear.
It's really delicious.
You think so?
Do you mean that?
That's such a relief.
I'm so happy you like it.
Now go ahead and heat up. Don't hold back.
There's plenty more where that came from.
Yeah, keep it coming!
I'm nowhere near full!
Hey!
Hey, you guys!
Young Master! Who's that?
It's those guys.
Wait! Don't go!
Oh, you can't leave before
I get to say thank you.
Handsome, well, obviously.
But it's me, Devil.
Wait, doesn't his face look different?
I rearranged his bone structure.
Now the creep's got nothing
to gripe and moan about.
Why, young master blackleg, I was
surprised after you kicked my face.
But I can't deny the results are amazing.
Look, look how ravishing
and handsome you've made me!
I'm a different person.
Wow, the ladies are gonna go nuts over me.
I must say life's starting to look? Rosy.
I love it all.
I want to do now is head back to
the countryside and take it easy.
But there's no way I could
leave without thanking you.
I'd be paralyzed with guilt if I did.
It's your first time in
this part of the sea.
So if there's anything we can do to help
you out, do not hesitate to call on us.
Don't wink until your
face is settled well.
As long as you're happy,
that's more than enough.
If you really want to pay me
back, don't bother us anymore.
So handsome, I'm beautiful.
Are you even listening to me?
I belong atop a white stallion.
Hey, listen, head.
Hey, head, listen.
to the guy, will ya?
Did he say
I'm handsome?
I didn't say anything remotely like that!
You want me to turn your face
back into the wanted poster?
Blowing me a kiss is a bit forward.
But nonetheless, I accept. Woo-hoo!
I didn't blow you a kiss!
I was just wiping all
this sauce off my lips!
you're so overconfident you're
delusional mirror mirror in my hand
I'm the handsomest in the lab
you know it really doesn't matter
how handsome you are you're still
an idiot oh you're jealous I'm
not give it up who stop you can't
talk about it being crazy well
young master and friends here's
my transponder snail number call
me anytime you can count on my
assistance day or night I owe it
to you after all I've put you
through I do apologize for all the
trouble sorry all right Rosie
life riders ho hurry up and leave
That was some good eating Every
bite of it What a truly splendid
afternoon My first taste of octopus
fritters And hopefully not my last
Oh, do excuse me
Everything about you is nasty
I'm worn out They sure know how to eat.
They must have broken some kind of record.
I really could have used six
more arms Awesome work, Hatchan!
It looks like they're all satisfied?
Oh yeah?
Then I'm satisfied too That was amazing.
I'm about to burst!
Hey, octopus, starfish, you too, Kuma?
Come take a break up on deck.
I'll make you a cup of tea Sure
It looks like you guys
are on the right course.
First stop Sabaody Archipelago
and we've got to go there first.
If we want to get to Fish Man Island,
we fish men and mermaids could dive right
down and get there in no time at all.
It's not quite so easy for humans.
The water pressure would crush
you to bits if you tried.
Yeah.
No joke.
It was too much for the
Sharks Emerge to handle. Ahem.
Folks, attention, please.
It's clear to me that
you're downright clueless,
so allow me to enlighten you
about the sea around these parts.
Wait, who will enlighten them?
Well, I suppose that would be...
this guy.
Yeah, that sounds pretty good to me.
Um, will you please listen to me? Huh?
Ahem.
First off,
there are actually two separate routes
one can travel to reach the New World.
But for outlaws such as yourselves,
only one of them is a viable option.
Why is that?
Oh, I'll tell ya. You see,
the first route passes
over the Red Line and
directly through the
sacred land of Marijua,
which is protected by the world government
and requires their permission to enter.
Huh?
The world government's not exactly fond
of pirates, so I doubt you'd get through.
You've gotta cross the
Red Line on foot that way?
How do people get their ships across?
The common practice is
for people to leave their
ships behind and buy a
new one on the other side.
They abandoned their ships! Yep.
You've got to apply to get permission,
so it takes time and money,
but it is the safest way to get across.
Good news for you, though!
The passage you'll be taking, you
don't have to get rid of your ship!
And that passage is the
Great Seafloor Route!
Straight through Fishman Island!
The thing is, the seafloor
route is pretty dangerous.
Excuse me, Kuma, Kuma, I
wasn't finished talking yet.
Hey. All the time.
Yeah, that counts.
Hey, Kuma.
Definitely dangerous.
I'll take it from here.
You know, I don't want to go
to Fishman Island after all.
Yeah, me neither.
Hey, wait, Kuma.
Did you say their ships
get eaten? Huh? Yeah.
What kind of ship will get
us across the sea floor?
This one's fine. Huh?
No.
Oh, this ship's not equipped
to travel underwater.
Sure, but it will be. Huh?
The thing is, the red line may be the
most massive wall in the whole world,
but it's not totally solid.
And there's one small hole
that passes through it.
Well, small in the big picture.
To us, it's super huge.
And inside that hole
is Fishman Island. New!
It's actually right beneath
the sacred land of Mariejoie.
All you do is dive down about 30,000
feet, and there it is in all its glory.
That far?
Trust me, it's worth the trip.
Then again, I guess we went about 30,000
feet in the air to get to Sky Pia.
But taking this ship
underwater, how's that possible?
Oh, we're going to get the ship coated
when we reach the island we're headed to.
Coat it with what?
Hey, look up ahead!
We're here, everybody!
It's beautiful!
It sure is.
Wow, what's all that
stuff floating around?
Oh, my.
It's like a dream.
Bubbles.
This is it.
The Sabaody Archipelago.
I've never seen so many
bubbles in my life.
So pretty.
Uh, it's just an endless barrage of them.
Where the heck are they coming from?
And who's blowing all of them? No one.
The island makes them.
Wait, what?
Yeah, explain.
Mind if I interrupt?
Sorry, I'm not trying to be rude.
But what does the log post say?
Oh, right. Just one sec.
The needle's still pointing
toward Fishman Island.
Let's just hope that this island
isn't going to rewrite the log on us.
You. It's fine.
The Savoote Archipelago is
just a cluster of trees.
There's no magnetic field.
It's not actually a real island.
Right.
Are you guys familiar with mangrove trees?
Mangroves?
Trees with roots above or under the
water, depending on the tides, right?
Yep, you got it.
But the tide never rises high enough
here for the roots to be submerged.
The Savoote Archipelago is home to the
largest mangrove trees in the world.
These colossal giants are
the Hustle Muscle mangroves.
The largest mangroves in the world?
Those are some manly mangroves!
This place is great!
There's a total of 79 trees, and each
one serves as its own little island,
complete with tiny towns and facilities.
The cluster of all these trees is
known as the Sabaody Archipelago.
Grove 44 appears the private
residence entrance, so before we land,
we'll need to go a little further in.
Wow, when you see them up
close, these roots are huge!
is that a man-made bridge it
is bridges connect each one of
the islands I see that makes
sense all right we're here this is
a good spot to drop anchor
welcome to Grove 41
hey
make sure
you all remember the grove number
okay like Like I said earlier,
the whole archipelago is connected
by a series of bridges so
you won't get lost if you remember
the number you're docked at.
There's one guy that'll still get lost.
Yep.
Huh? What's going on?
Hey, what was that for?
A bubble popped out of the ground!
What the weird is that?
Awesome!
I'm riding it!
That is one strong bubble!
Wow!
These soap bubbles, I'm curious.
How exactly do they get produced?
I got this one.
It's a chemical reaction from
the hustle muscle mangrove roots.
They secrete a unique
resin that causes it.
Ugh, it's really sticky.
Hey, stop that!
You see, when the roots
of the trees breathe,
the air inflates the resin as
it rises out of the ground.
Interesting.
I never would have thought
tree sap could flow.
Wow, so this is all 100 % natural. Hey!
Huh?
Luffy, where did you get
all the way up there?
There's an amusement park over there!
Let's go!
We want to ride the ferris wheel!
Oh my gosh, really?
Yeah, that's Sabaody Park.
Oh, wow, I'm so jealous.
See, I've always dreamed of
riding that ferris wheel.
You have?
Why don't you just write it?
Not a chance.
Don't you even think about it.
Yeah, I know. Don't remind me.
If she can't write it, does
that mean I can't either?
So, Hachi, what's our objective
on this island anyway?
Didn't you say something before
about getting the ship coated here?
We'll meet up with one of the
island's coating specialists
and have him slap a coat
of this resin on your ship.
Huh?
That's all it takes.
After that, your ship will be fully
equipped for underwater travel.
Seriously?
Yep, the process works wonders,
and it's the only way I know of that
humans can reach Fishman Island.
But you don't want an amateur to do it.
If it's not done right, the water pressure
will crush the ship and everyone on it.
I've got one specialist that I really
trust, though, so you'll be in good hands.
thank you for your help you really
are a good man wait good octopus
but first in exchange for
my help promise me one thing
sure what is it once we cross
the bridge into town there's
a chance we might run into
the world nobles okay who
the world nobles they're
from the Holy Land Marie Joie
Cool!
So what's the big deal?
This is difficult to ask, but no
matter what happens in the town,
you must promise that you'll do
nothing to defy the world nobles.
I'll say it one more time.
No matter what, you act
like you didn't see a thing!
Everyone else went to town.
Why didn't the two of you go with them?
We used up a lot of cola
in that battle with Devil.
Damn near all of it.
It's my job to take good care of the sun.
That's right.
And I like helping out with
all things ship-related, too.
Once we're done, all three
of us can head out together.
What do you say?
Sound good?
Sorry.
Thanks for the invite,
but I can't do my shopping until
a certain someone comes back.
Wait, what do you mean?
Oh, you see...
My beloved Nami was in a jam.
Hmm.
Now what to do?
We have a ton of treasure on board,
and I can't leave the ship
knowing it's unguarded.
If only there was a valiant
knight around to keep an eye on.
Ha-ha! That's me!
She's got you wrapped around
her finger, doesn't she?
I am a slave to love!
You admitting it saves me the trouble.
Hey! Zoro! Zoro! Wait!
Where do you think you're
going all by yourself?
For a walk
Is that okay? Of course not!
You're gonna get yourself lost, moron!
This is an archipelago!
We won't be able to find you!
Screw you!
I'm not gonna get lost!
Only an idiot would get
turned around in a place
like this All of these
trees have numbers on them,
okay?
That way it doesn't matter how bad
your sense of direction is Whoa!
Nice job!
You actually put some thought into this
Yeah, good call Alright then, have fun!
Ask for directions if you get confused.
Don't trust your instincts!
Screw these guys.
I'll be all right.
I just have to remember
the number on this tree.
And that number is one.
What do they think I can't count?
I have to be brained to get
lost in a place like this.
I'm not taking any more crap from them.
The world nobles I mentioned are
also known as the Celestial Dragons.
They think they're so much
better than everyone else,
they wear masks to avoid
breathing the same air as us.
Now remember what I said.
No matter what they do,
just stay out of their way.
I need you to promise me that.
Aside from that,
there are a couple of other things you
should probably keep an eye out for.
Remember, this is the place everyone
gathers before heading to the New World.
In other words, like you, there are a
lot of big-name pirate crews around,
which means Marines and bounty
hunters are out to catch them.
Also, the law won't protect pirates
from being bought and sold here.
Kidnapping happens all the time.
So try not to stand out.
If people realize how much you're worth,
the whole island will be on you and
we'll never get the ship coated.
And fair warning, the Marines
here aren't pushovers.
We're right by Navy headquarters, so you
never know which powerhouses might show up.
The bounty hunters here
are pretty ferocious, too.
They're a lot tougher
than what you're used to.
Oh, yeah, and one more thing.
Oh, come on.
We're going to be just fine.
Kuma is no mermaid,
and I'm not a fish man.
Not while we're here, anyway.
Just pretend we're humans like you.
What?
Why would we do that?
When traveling, it's best to
honor the local culture, Luffy.
Let's just do what the octopus asks.
That's it.
Slowly.
Look, I'm inside!
I'll be next! How mysterious.
I can get my whole body in here, and
none of the air is coming out either.
You ain't seen nothing yet.
Here, pull this thing
inside there with you.
Like this?
As long as you can reach the pedals, you
can drive it around all over the place.
Ah!
It's moving!
Ah! Ah!
Here it goes! Woo-hoo!
The bubble isn't breaking.
These bubble bites are the most convenient
way to get around the
Zeff Odi acapella goal.
They're affordable, too.
They rent for 500 berries a person, but
you can own it for only 10,000 berries.
So how about it?
We'll just rent one. Wait!
I got the money.
I'm going to buy one.
Me too! Me too! Yeah.
No, you don't.
There's no point in buying.
Just rent it.
It's my money.
I'll do what I want.
Yeah, so that.
Well, um, look, take my word for it.
I'll explain everything later.
Two rentals, please.
I take it you're a local, then.
Such a shame.
Wow!
This is fantastic.
I love it.
You can't stop me.
I'm gonna buy one of these.
Listen, Straw Hat,
think back to when you rode that bubble
up into the sky right after we got here.
Do you remember what happened to it?
Uh,
yeah, I hopped on a bubble, flew
up past the tops of the trees,
and tried to jump around to
other ones to go even higher.
But out of nowhere, all the
bubbles around me started popping.
And the one I was riding on popped too.
And then I fell down.
That happened because you left the Sabo
Odi Archipelago's unique atmosphere.
This area has a distinct climate specifically
suited to the Hustle Muscle mangroves.
Once you leave that climate, the
resin in the bubble starts to change.
Not long after that, they pop.
Really?
That means someone would
only be able to ride
one of these bubbles if
they stayed in this area,
correct? Yeah.
See, you get it.
People who come here for the first time
are always eager to buy a bubble bike.
Since they only work here, it's a rip-off.
Just renting one is all you really need.
I don't care!
I want to buy one!
All I heard was blub,
blub, blub, bubble bite.
How many ways do we have
to spell it out for you?
Once you leave this island, the
bubbles aren't strong enough.
They just pop.
It's quite the mystery, isn't it?
Whoa, what the hell?
They're mystery bubbles?
Why didn't you say so before? We did.
Why don't you ever listen?
Oh, you can use bubble bites on
Fishman Island, too, if you like.
The ocean floor has the
same kind of bubbles.
You'll love it.
Ooh, I can't wait to
get to Fishman Island.
It's going to be awesome.
In that case, you should
meet the mermaid princess.
So graceful, so beautiful.
Sometimes it's all you can
do not to stare at her.
I look forward to it.
I have an excellent eye
for appreciating beauty.
Though being a skeleton, I
don't actually have any eyes.
Do you get it?
That stuff looks yummy! It's a grammon.
A gram-line steamed buns.
They're called grammon for short.
Care to try a sample?
As you can see, it's got Grand
Line First Half written into it.
They're meant to be a
souvenir to return home with.
Shelf life's three months.
Plenty of time to make it back with them.
Delicious!
Would it be all right if I
sampled another box or two?
Aren't you gonna buy any?
Grove 35.
There seem to be a lot
of hotels around here.
Those are the living
quarters of the sailors who
are waiting for permission
to pass through Marijua.
Building all these hotels
is easier than you'd think.
See?
They simply coat the giant soap
bubbles with a metal alloy and Fall!
Instant foundation.
That's how all the round
buildings are made.
Wow.
Robin!
Amal, I bet they have all sorts of stuff.
Let's check it out.
Stop by any time!
Cratchaco!
And crackers, too! A
keychain! And a pudding!
Hold on to those precious memories!
You guys bought a lot of stuff.
It'll be tough to carry
all that junk around.
Go have him bubble pack it up for you.
What's a bubble pack?
Awesome, it's so light!
Carrying around stuff in
this place is super easy.
Hey, where are Robin and Nami?
Don't worry about them.
They went to the shopping
mall on Grove 30.
They said that they wanted to leave
the coating of the ship to us.
Oh, yeah?
Right, leave it to us then.
So where are we headed next, Hachi?
We're going to Grove 31.
Even by bike, it's a long trip,
so we should probably get moving.
I wonder why Kuma didn't join us.
We invited her. Yeah.
She's been sort of nervous and quiet
ever since we got here, hasn't she?
Something's bothering her,
but I don't know what.
Perhaps it's Sabo O .D.
itself.
There could be a bad
history tied to the island.
A bad history, huh?
Yeah!
I'm winning!
Don't get so cocky!
We've still got a long way
to go! Yeah! Keep it up!
You can do it, Hanson!
What the heck is happening, you guys?
Why did this turn into some kind of race?
Yeah!
Yeah! Yeah!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
Hey, what's all I yelling about?
Anybody, please, get me
out of this damn thing!
Bring me something!
Somebody bring me a damn tool!
An axe, a saw, something
to get this thing off me!
All I want is to go back home.
I don't want to hurt anybody
I give up.
I don't want to go to the
new world anymore, please.
I've got a wife and kid back
home I'm begging you here.
Somebody help me
My little boy.
I left when he was just a baby.
He doesn't even know what I look like
Help me please who's that I want
to go home that's all that matters
now I won't hurt you let's stay
Out of this he's probably just some
pirate who was caught by kidnappers
and sold into slavery His owner
must have brought him to this
island and then he made a run for it
But he must know what happens
to slaves who try to get away
What's that sound? Why is it ticking?
This collar!
If I could only get this thing
off my neck! Stop it! Please!
Stop ticking! Damn it! Damn it!
Get off me!
Help me.
Every slave has one of those metal
collars put around their neck.
And if they try to take it off or
run from their master, it'll explode.
Just let me go home to my family.
I don't want to be a pirate
in the new world anymore.
Ah!
It's a slave that tried to escape!
Everybody, stay back! Ignore him!
I can't believe what just happened.
We have to help!
Idiot, you guys promised not to get
involved no matter what, remember?
Ah!
What's with this crazy place?
What are we gonna do, Hachi?
And the Celestial Dragons
will be here any minute!
It's all right.
Just stay calm, Kuma.
Listen, Straw Hat, you need to get
off that bubble bike. What for?
Hurry up and do it!
Fine.
Just this once.
They're here.
That's not a dragon. Bow down! But why?
No matter what happens,
don't look them in the eye.
Same goes for you guys.
Right.
Saru, come now.
Don't be vulgar.
Those are dragons. Yeah.
Oh, look, Father.
Another one of our slaves has broken down.
Did you give it its daily sedative
like you were supposed to?
Of course I did.
But it seems it had no
effect on this poor fool.
I don't even want it anymore.
Would you buy me a new one?
Honestly, you're terrible
at taking care of them.
You're decimating my precious ship
captain collection one pirate at a time.
It was useless to begin
with. Family. Children.
Stop crying.
Pathetic.
You're nothing but a lowly human slave.
She can't even move.
You make me want to vomit!
Shut down, control yourself.
I think I'd like a
giant for my next slave.
Perhaps something smaller,
like a human child.
I detest the weak ones.
Whatever you're thinking,
don't think about it?
The Marines!
We need to get the hell
away from here, fast!
Would you care for some tea?
It'll calm your nerves.
Uh-uh.
I feel terrible. Thanks, though.
You think he's gonna be all right?
Maybe so, but if he lives,
he'll go to prison for piracy.
I don't understand.
An old man and a woman are no
match for a pirate like that.
What's going on here?
If anyone hurts a celestial dragon,
Navy Headquarters sends an admiral and a
fleet of battleships to
handle the situation.
An admiral?
You mean Aokiji?
It could be him or Aka 'inu or Kizaru.
No telling which one of them will show up.
Remember, we're right by HQ.
What makes those celestial
dragons so special?
The dragons are from the bloodline of
the creators of the world government.
Are you serious?
800 years ago a group of 20
kings came together to create
the organization that's now
known as the world government?
The Celestial Dragons
are their descendants
as the years go by
generation after generation!
They grow more and more
reckless with power!
Celestial dragons